If you have no idea where to start your Common App essay
or you're like halfway through the process
and don't know how to continue,
this is exactly the package for you
because this is where I walk you through every step
of getting your Common App essay ready to go.
I got into every single college that I applied to
and $600,000 in merit scholarships,
including a full tuition scholarship to Vanderbilt.
And since then, I've helped over a thousand students
write their college essays,
getting them into crazy schools
like NYU with full tuition, Vanderbilt with scholarship,
UC Berkeley with Regents scholarship, Penn Cornell,
Dartmouth, Rice, and so many more.
And I would love to help you too.
In this one-on-one package,
I will be walking you through the full step
of getting your Common App essay ready to go
using the same strategies
that I've used to help my students succeed.
If you've already started,
we can start based off of wherever you are in the process
but if you're starting from scratch,
here's how it will work.
We start with a brainstorming call
where I will walk you through
all of the seven Common App prompts
and I will help you figure out
what ideas to put down for each one,
which of your ideas are good, and how to expand on them.
And then I'm going to help you pick the best idea.
So I'm going to help you pick whichever one is most unique
because I've read a thousand essays
so I can definitely tell you what stands out.
And then I'm going to help you create an outline for it
so that you know exactly what to put in your essay
to make it stand out and shine.
And then after that,
we're just going to work on revising your essay.
It's a simple process
and it has worked with so many students
and I've gotten the beauty
of getting to see people go from idea
to perfectly polished essay
through these sessions with me.
The best part is that in between each of our calls,
you have unlimited access to me through email.
So if you have any quick questions
about what to do in between calls,
if you get stuck,
are not sure if you want to pursue an idea,
just email me and I'll get back to you
and give you the help that you need to stay unstuck.
This package genuinely gives you peace of mind
because you know that you're doing your Common App right
the whole way through
and you never have to feel lost, stuck,
or wonder what's going on.
So it's one that my students have really loved.
That being said though,
if you do struggle to make time to schedule calls,
I also offer an asynchronous version of this package
where you can just get written edits on your Common App.
But I wouldn't recommend that for you
if you are just now starting the process from scratch
and need help actually picking a topic.
That's more for students who already have things written.
I would absolutely love to work with you.
So email me at avigallang at gmail.com
if you have any questions about this package
and otherwise you can book right here on my website
while I still have availability.
I cannot wait to work with you.